export const data=[
    {
        question:"What is the correct command to create a new React project?",
        option1:"npx create-react-app myReactApp",
        option2:"npm create-react-app",
        option3:"npm create-react-app",
        option4:"npm create-react-app myReactApp",
        ans:1,
    },
    {
        question:"What does myReactApp refer to in the following command?",
        option1:"A reference to an existing app",
        option2:"The type of app to create",
        option3:"The directory to create the new app in",
        option4:"The name you want to use for the new app",
        ans:4,
    },
    {
        question:"What command is used to start the React local development server?",
        option1:"npm serve",
        option2:"npm start",
        option3:"npm build",
        option4:"npm run dev",
        ans:2,
    },
    {
        question:"What is the default local host port that a React development server uses?",
        option1:"8080",
        option2:"5000",
        option3:"3000",
        option4:"3500",
        ans:3,
    },
    {
        question:"What is the children prop?",
        option1:"A property that lets you pass data to child components",
        option2:"A property that lets you nest components in other components",
        option3:"A property that adds child values to state",
        option4:"A property that lets you set an object as a property",
        ans:2,
    },
    {
        question:"Which keyword creates a constant in JavaScript?",
        option1:"var",
        option2:"let",
        option3:"constant",
        option4:"const",
        ans:4,
    },
    {
        question:"A copy of the 'real' DOM that is keptin memory is called what?",
        option1:"DOM",
        option2:"React DOM",
        option3:"Virtual DOM",
        option4:"Shadow DOM",
        ans:3,
    },
    {
        question:"Which operator can be used to conditionally render a React component?",
        option1:"&&",
        option2:"::",
        option3:"||",
        option4:"??",
        ans:1,
    },
    {
        question:"When rendering a list using the JavaScript map() method, what is required for each element rendered?",
        option1:"key",
        option2:"id",
        option3:"data",
        option4:"index",
        ans:1,
    },
    {
        question:"How can you optimize performance for a function component that always renders the same way?",
        option1:"Use the shouldComponentUpdate lifecycle method.",
        option2:"Use the useMemo Hook",
        option3:"Use the useReducer Hook",
        option4:"Wrap it in the React.memo higher-order component.",
        ans:4,
    }   
]